[
  {
    "question": "_____ am * .",
    "correctAnswer": "I",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["My", "You", "Your"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Dave", "Sam", "Dean", "Eric", "Victor", "Nate", "Chuck", "Dan", "Kevin", "Tom", "Mike", "Tim", "Stan", "Peter", "Damon", "Steve", "Betty", "Veronica", "Kate", "Blair", "Serena", "Vanessa", "Margo", "Bella", "Alice", "Stella", "Penny", "Erica", "Ann", "Carla", "Maria", "Lizzy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is * .",
    "correctAnswer": "He",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["They", "Our", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Dave", "Sam", "Dean", "Eric", "Victor", "Nate", "Chuck", "Dan", "Kevin", "Tom", "Mike", "Tim", "Stan", "Peter", "Damon", "Steve"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is * .",
    "correctAnswer": "She",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["I", "We", "Their"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["Betty", "Veronica", "Kate", "Blair", "Serena", "Vanessa", "Margo", "Bella", "Alice", "Stella", "Penny", "Erica", "Ann", "Carla", "Maria", "Lizzy"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ am * .",
    "correctAnswer": "I",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["We", "My", "They"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is * .",
    "correctAnswer": "She",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["His", "Her", "You"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is * .",
    "correctAnswer": "He",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Her", "We", "His"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["two years old", "three years old", "four years old", "five years old", "six years old", "seven years old", "eight years old", "nine years old", "ten years old", "eleven", "twelve", "thirteen", "fourteen", "fifteen", "sixteen", "seventeen", "eighteen", "nineteen", "twenty"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is a * .",
    "correctAnswer": "It",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["His", "My", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "fox", "bear", "wolf", "lion", "giraffe", "monkey", "banana", "moon", "star", "heart", "square", "triangle", "circle", "cloud", "hat", "scarf", "cucumber", "tomato", "potato", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is _____ a * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "it",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["our", "their", "you"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "fox", "bear", "wolf", "lion", "giraffe", "monkey", "banana", "moon", "star", "heart", "square", "triangle", "circle", "cloud", "hat", "scarf", "cucumber", "tomato", "potato", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ am from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "I",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["We", "He", "She"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "She",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["My", "I", "They"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ is from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "He",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Your", "You", "We"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ are from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "We",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Their", "Our", "Your"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ are from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "You",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Your", "He", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "_____ are from * .",
    "correctAnswer": "They",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["Our", "My", "She"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are _____ from * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "they",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["their", "her", "he"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["New York", "Mexico", "Cape Town", "Budapest", "Tokio", "Berlin", "Paris", "Madrid", "Helsinki", "Vienna", "Chicago", "Milan", "Washington", "London", "America", "France", "Germany", "Australia", "Italy", "Spain", "Brazil", "Kazakhstan"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "my",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "you", "we"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "his",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "I", "they"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "her",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["she", "we", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "our",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["we", "you", "he"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "This is _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "their",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["I", "she", "they"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this _____ * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "my",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["I", "we", "she"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this _____ * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "your",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["he", "they", "you"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Is this _____ * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "his",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["she", "we", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["dog", "cat", "horse", "hamster", "parrot", "toy", "pet", "hat", "scarf", "balloon", "doll", "ball", "kite", "scooter", "plane", "train", "ship", "car", "bus", "phone", "computer"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are these _____ * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "their",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["they", "she", "he"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "Are these _____ * ?",
    "correctAnswer": "your",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["I", "we", "you"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These are _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "our",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["you", "they", "he"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These are _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "their",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["they", "we", "I"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  },
  {
    "question": "These are _____ * .",
    "correctAnswer": "your",
    "incorrectAnswers": ["she", "he", "you"],
    "endOfQuestion": ["parents", "grandparents", "friends", "mother and father", "sisters", "brothers", "brother and sister", "grandmother and grandfather", "gloves", "trousers", "socks", "shoes"]
  }
]